http://www.episcopalspringfield.org/privacy/

Diocese of Springfield
MenuAbout UsThe Episcopal ChurchOur Vision for MissionOur HistoryThe Diocese of SpringfieldOur ChurchesDiocesan StaffDiocesan Documents & ReportsNational and World MissionsOur Companion DiocesesTabora Trip CloseMinistriesLiturgy and MusicPrayers of the PeopleSung Psalms for the EucharistBishop’s Liturgical CustomaryHoly Week Passion ReadingsChristian Formation ResourcesProclaiming the Gospel 101Patterns of MinistryReading the Bible for DummiesCursilloUnpacking LentOccupying Our Baptismal CovenantN. T. Wright OnlineSeven HabitsOutreach MinistriesUnited Thank Offering (UTO)Episcopal Church WomenEpiscopal Church Camp CloseDaily LifeLicensed Lay MinistriesBlogSynod 2020Pandemic ResourcesDiocesan ResourcesNotes from the BishopResurrecting Worship CloseBishop SearchTimelineBishop Search Q&ACommitteesNewsContact CloseCalendarsDiocesan CalendarPrayer Calendar CloseBishop’s CornerBishop’s BioPastoral Letters, Etc.Moving Diagonally: Daily
JournalSermonsFormal Portraits CloseConnect With UsThe Current ArchiveDiocesan PublicationsContact Us Close
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Episcopal Diocese of Springfield collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the episcopalspringfield.org website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Episcopal Diocese of Springfield.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Episcopal Diocese of Springfield may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Changes to this privacy policy
Episcopal Diocese of Springfield has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Episcopal Diocese of Springfield
episcopalspringfield.org
Episcopal Diocese of Springfield
821 South Second Street
Springfield, Illinois
62704
(217) 525-1876
diocese@episcopalspringfield.org
This document was last updated on February 23, 2015
Episcopal News ServiceSouthern Ohio Bishop Thomas Breidenthal retires after 13 years leading dioceseNew bishop for prisons welcomed by Church of England and Church in WalesTongan royal family helps with prayer book translationNorth Carolina ministry promotes health care access, rooted in bonds formed over prayer, food
Links
Anglican Communion
Anglican Communion News Service
Archbishop of Canterbury
Continuing Indaba
Diocese of Tabora
Forward Movement
Living Reconciliation
